A Guide to the Beverly Repass Hoch Miscellaneous Collection, 1833-1924
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Beverly Repass Hoch Miscellaneous Collection 1833-1924
Special Collections, Kegley Library
2008.5
2 folders.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Beverly Repass Hoch in 2008; material in Folder 2 donated in 2011.
Scope and Content
The documents in this collection were purchased by professional genealogist Beverly Repass Hoch from eBay in 2008 and 2011. Mrs. Hoch donated the contents of Folder 4 in 2008 and the contents of Folder 2 in 2011.
Contents List
- Folder 1. 2008 Collection. 1889, 1911, undated, 4 items.
  - Certificate of Residence. Helen Shelburne. 23 July 1889., 1 p.
    Certificate stating that Helen Shelburne, currently age 21, is residing at the home of Rev. A. A. Ferguson, Wytheville, Virginia.
  - Letter. John P. Summers, Abingdon, Virginia to County Court Clerk. 21 September 1889., 1 p.
    Re: request for search of land records for Henry Copenhaver who died ca. 1827. whose heirs in Iowa are trying to establish claim through his son George Copenhaver.
  - Letter. Walter S. Tipton, Hillsville, Virginia to Capt. E. Rogers, Ivanhoe, Virginia. 11 December 1911., 1 p.; envelope.
    Re: congratulations on his recent divorce.
  - Letter. Sue M. Young, Mt. Airy Depot, Virginia to Jennie [unknown]. 2 August [unknown]., 2 p.
    Re: heavy rain, Sunday School at Oak Grove Chapel (later Hawkins Chapel Lutheran Church).
- Folder 2. 2011 Addendum. 1833-1924., 10 items.
  - Letter. B. Estill, Wythe Court House, Virginia to Samuel McCamant, Grayson Court House, Virginia. 19 December 1833., 2 p.
    Re: request to check for missing paper in court case of Thompson vs. Sayers et al.
  - Letter. Anne Dabney Stuart Brown, Wythe Court House, Virginia to Jane Lewis Stuart Crockett, Christiansburg, Virginia. 10 January 1838., 4 p.
    Re: return of husband, James Ewell Brown; her rheumatism; family; slaves Edwin and Rosannah; children of Jane Lewis Crockett including Charles Lewis Crockett, Gustavus Crockett and wife Elizabeth Erskine Crockett, Francis Crockett; death of William Brown's child; and Methodist revival and religion.
  - Letter. Mary McKee, Wytheville, Virginia to Eliza McKee, c/o Mrs. Jno. McKee, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 30 December 1841, 4 p.
    Re: Christmas and spiritual matters; Methodist church and preachers; illness of their uncle, Adam McKee; Dr. Chapman of Philadelphia; Emory and Henry College ministers; teacher Jane Hamilton Childs; and family.
  - Letter. John Ewing, Wythe County, Virginia to James V. Ewing, Lewisburg, Marshall County, Tennessee. 10 June 1843., 4 p.
    Re: sickness in Wythe County; death of Catherine Painter, widow of Mathias Painter; illness of wife Polly (Mary) Ewing; Henry Ewing; drinking of Joshua Ewing; plans for his tannery.
  - Letter. Robert Gibboney, Wytheville, Virginia to Hugh M. Sheffey, Richmond, Virginia. 15 January 1849., 2 p.
    Re: payment for creditors of Hayden H. Bell.
  - Letter. Charles B. Shaw, Wytheville, Virginia to A. B. McFarlan, Washington, D. C.. 18 April 1849., 3 p.
    Re: road conditions.
  - Letter. Thomas Wood, Max Meadows, Virginia to Anne E. Wood, Poplar Hill, Giles County, Virginia. 5 August 1879., 3 p.; envelope.
    Re: her stay and treatment at Pulaski Alum Springs; his trip home; neighbors including Joseph Crockett; Guy Sanders; his incredulity at how ladies walk in high heeled shoes on macadamized streets in Newbern, Virginia.
  - Letter. I. H. Rhorer, Wytheville, Virginia to Eliza Rhorer, [unknown]. 9 January 1893., 4 p.
    Re: death of Polly Cooper; call of Rev. T. P. Barclay to Wytheville Presbyterian Church; healthy climate of Wytheville.
  - Notice. John H. Puckett, Bank of Ivanhoe, Ivanhoe, Virginia to W. H. Slater. 12 June 1923., 1 p.
  - Check. Nannie B. Slater, First National Bank, Wytheville, Virginia. 23 February 1924., 1 p.